[{"question":"# Q1. What type of relationship is defined as one resource existing only if another parent resource exist-for example, pages in a book?","options":["Partial","dependent","associative","linked"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Partial"},{"question":"# Q2. Which URL pattern s recommended when working with one resource and a collection of resources?","options":["/companies/{id} and/company","/company/{id} and/companies","/companies/{id} and/companies","/company/{id} and/company"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"/companies/{id} and/companies"},{"question":"# Q3. When dealing with JSON web Tokens (JWTs), what is a claim?","options":["data in the token","Ownership","a permission","and integer"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"data in the token"},{"question":"# Q4. Which REST contraint specifies that knowledge and understanding obtained from one component of the API should be generally applicable elsewhere in the API?","options":["Uniform Interface","Client-Server","Stateless","Chacheable"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Uniform Interface"},{"question":"# Q5. What would you enable to allow a browser on another site to make an AJAX request to your API?","options":["HTTP","REST","OPTIONS","CORS"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"CORS"},{"question":"# Q6. APIs commonly use webhooks to `**\\*\\*\\*\\***\\_\\_\\_\\_**\\*\\*\\*\\***`.","options":["notify other systems of an event","catch error faster","improve error logging","log additional data"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"notify other systems of an event"},{"question":"# Q7. What is the underlying goal of all APIs?","options":["to add new technologies to an organization's infrastructure.","to share features and functionality with other system.","to move infrastructure to the cloud.","to appease the latest digital transformation effort."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"to share features and functionality with other system."},{"question":"# Q8. Which is a common command-line tool for using or exploring an API?","options":["bash","curl","ssh","powerShell"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"curl"},{"question":"# Q9. What is the modern specification for describing an API?","options":["OpenAPI (Swagger)","WADL","WSDL","OAuth"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"OpenAPI (Swagger)"},{"question":"# Q10. Which HTTP verb is normally used to update or create a resource in an API?","options":["SUBMIT","WRITE","POST","CREATE"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"POST"},{"question":"# Q11. What is one benefit of server-side caching in APIs?","options":["Mobile app work better.","It improves uptime.","It offers better security.","It reduce load on servers."],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"It reduce load on servers."},{"question":"# Q12. Your API resource does no allow deletion, and a client application attempted to delete the resource. What HTTP respose code should you return?","options":["409 Conflict","400 Bad Request","406 Not Acceptable","405 Method Not Allowed"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"405 Method Not Allowed"},{"question":"# Q13. What is OpenID Connect?","options":["an identify layer on top of OAuth 2.0","the new name for SAML 3.0","a modern replacement for API keys","an SSO competitor for OAuth 2.0"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"an identify layer on top of OAuth 2.0"},{"question":"# Q14. What is one benefit of GraphQl over REST approaches?","options":["flexible querying/responses","more stable APIs","compatible with more gateways","more secure by default"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"flexible querying/responses"},{"question":"# Q15. Which REST constraint specifies that there should be no shared context?","options":["Stateless","Client-Server","Uniform Interface","Cacheable"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"Stateless"},{"question":"# Q16. What purpose does a User-Agent serve?","options":["It identifies the user ID.","It identifies the client application or SDK.","It identifies if the API should expect a user authentication.","It identifies if the API should accept microservice traffic."],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"It identifies the client application or SDK."},{"question":"# Q17. If you were to add versioning by using the Accept and Content-Type header, what would be the correct format of the header value?","options":["application/json","application/json_version2","text/html","application/vnd.myapp.v2+json"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"text/html"},{"question":"# Q18. What is one benefit that OAuth provides over an API key approach?","options":["A token is encrypted.","A token is encoded.","A token is scoped to the use case.","A token can be shared between systems."],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"A token is scoped to the use case."},{"question":"# Q19. The ability to execute the same API request over and over again without changing the resource's state is an example of **\\_**.","options":["stateless architecture","idempotency","a uniform interface","cacheability"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"idempotency"},{"question":"# Q20. What component can you use to wrap legacy architectures or protocols into a REST interface for easier consumption and integration?","options":["API proxy","API gateway","OpenAPI","OAuth authorization server"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"API proxy"},{"question":"# Q21. What protection does a JSON Web Token (JWT) offer to mitigate tampering with its contents?","options":["transport over SSL","encrypted payload","a signature","encoded payload"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"a signature"},{"question":"# Q22. What OAuth term is used to represent permissions?","options":["token","scope","claim","back channel"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"scope"},{"question":"# Q23. What additional type of token would you see when using OpenID Connect?","options":["ID token","refresh token","access token","auth code token"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"ID token"},{"question":"# Q24. What should you add to a Cache-Control response header to specify that a response should not be stored in an intermediary cache?","options":["no-proxy","client-only","restricted","private` ","  [reference](https://www.digitalocean.com/community/tutorials/web-caching-basics-terminology-http-headers-and-caching-strategies)"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"private` "},{"question":"# Q25. Which OAuth grant type can support a refresh token?","options":["Authorization Code Grant","Client Credentials Grant","Implicit Grant","Authentication Grant"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"Client Credentials Grant"},{"question":"# Q26. Using OAuth, what scope would you request for write access to the API?","options":["It varies from API to API.","admin","write","read-write"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"admin"},{"question":"# Q27. Which property would you use to include subresources directly into a JSON document?","options":["\\_embedded","resources","subresources","\\_links"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"subresources"},{"question":"# Q28. What is the best way to track SDK and version usage?","options":["tracking downloads","Accept headers","user agents","polling users"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"tracking downloads"},{"question":"# Q29. Which REST constraint allows for the presence of caching, routing, and other systems between the client and server?","options":["Layered System","Stateless","Client-Server","Cacheable"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"Client-Server"},{"question":"# Q30. Which content is best to include in your documentation?","options":["your tech stack","reasoning for your naming schema","your mission statement","sample code"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"sample code"},{"question":"# Q31. What metric tracks overall availability for your API?","options":["Response Time","Time to First Hello World","TTL","Uptime"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Uptime"},{"question":"# Q32. What is the recommended method and URL pattern for retrieving a specific user?","options":["GET /user/{id}","GET /users/{id}","GET /user?id={id}","GET /users?id={id}"],"anwserIndex":1,"answerText":"GET /users/{id}"},{"question":"# Q33. What is the purpose of a link relation?","options":["to describe relationships between resources or actions","to describe subresources related to the current one","to link two resources together","to describe a resource and its purpose"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"to link two resources together"},{"question":"# Q34. When building SDKs, which languages should you support?","options":["Java, Javascript, and .NET","and you can support","PHP, Python, and Go","the languages that your target users use"]},{"question":"# Q35. Which property would you use to include references to other resources in a JSON document?","options":["resources","_embedded","subresources","_links"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"resources"},{"question":"# Q36. What is OAuth?","options":["an authorization framework for granted delegated access","an approach to single sign-on for APIs","a method for API authentication","HTTP Basic Authentication 2.0"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"an authorization framework for granted delegated access"},{"question":"# Q37. What should your API documentation describe?","options":["JSON","HTTP","common use cases","your tech stack"],"anwserIndex":2,"answerText":"common use cases"},{"question":"# Q38. What is the purpose of an OAuth refresh token?","options":["to share user profile information","to update an API configuration","to keep a web session active","to retrive an access token"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"to retrive an access token"},{"question":"# Q39. What is Time to First Hello World?","options":["how long it takes for a developer to do something with your API","how long it takes to start a new programming language","how long it takes to install your SDK","how long it takes to read your documentation"],"anwserIndex":0,"answerText":"how long it takes for a developer to do something with your API"},{"question":"# Q40. Which response header tells the client and intermediaries that the response is not to be cached anywhere?","options":["Cache-State: none","Expires:-1","Cache-Control: no-cache","Cache-Control: no-store"],"anwserIndex":3,"answerText":"Cache-Control: no-store"}]